Nancy Sweezy collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 9: Personal Files and Correspondence, 1923-2009
  - Subseries 1: Manuscripts and Photographic Prints
    - Photos (Garden, trees, water colors), 2007, afc2017001_cf03; digital images; original media: CD-ROM
    - Writings for memoir, undated, afc2017001_cf04; text files; original media: CD-ROM
    - Interview transcripts, undated, afc2017001_cf04; text files; original media: CD-ROM
    - Interview with Lybess, Sam, and Susan, 2006-07-22, afc2017001_cf04; text files; original media: CD-ROM
  - Subseries 2: Slides and Negatives
    - Unlabeled, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph24_023 to ph24_038; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - Dogs in snow, 1976, AFC 2017/001: ph24_039 to ph24_040; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - L's birthday party, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph24_041; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - AMC Scotland trip, 1989, AFC 2017/001: ph24_042 to ph24_044; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - Nancy at pottery, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph24_052 to ph24_053; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - Rob and M, 1985, AFC 2017/001: ph24_064; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - Sarah and weavers, 1985, AFC 2017/001: ph24_065; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - Unlabeled, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph24_066; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - Unlabeled, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph26_015 to ph26_047; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 47)